I'm Peppa Pig
and this is my little brother, George
This is Mummy Pig
and this is Daddy Pig
I'm Peppa Pig!
"The Time Capsule"
Peppa and her friends are at playgroup
Today, they are making a time capsule
What's a time capsule?
A time capsule is something that tells people in the future
how we live today
Pardon?
We put special things in a bucket
Then we bury it in the school garden
Will it grow?
No, Suzy
The bucket will stay underground for many years
Now, what should we put inside?
A comic book
Very good, Peppa
Music
Very good, Suzy
A toy
Coins
Stamps
A carrot
You really like carrots
don't you, Rebecca?
Yes
The things in this bucket
show what our everyday life is like
Madame Gazelle
I wonder what the future will be like?
Well, what do you think it will be like?
I think in the future, I will live on the Moon
and all my friends will come visit me on the Moon
And I will fly a space rocket in the future
Okay?
Now we will record a message for the people of the future
Everyone, say hello to the future
Hello, future, how are you?
I think you might be living on the Moon now
and going on holiday to Mars
and zooming around in rockets, too!
Very good
It's almost time to go home
All the parents have arrived
Mummy, Daddy, we made a time capsule!
Daddy Pig, you're just in time
Could you dig a hole for us?
Of course!
Daddy Pig has dug a hole in the school garden
to put the time capsule in
All done
Can we dig it up now?
It will stay underground
for many, many years
But I can't wait that long
Peppa
you're just like your daddy when he was little
Really?
Yes, I remember when I was his teacher too
You taught my daddy?
Yes, I taught all your daddies and mummies
Did you?
- Yes, Madame Gazelle
When your daddies and mummies were young
They made a time capsule too
Yes, that's right
We buried it next to a little tree
Can we dig it up?
Yes
I think we buried it here
I thought it was a very small tree
That was a long time ago
The tree is much bigger now
Look, I've found something
It's our old time capsule
- Hooray!
I can't wait to see inside
All right, everyone, stand back
- Yes, Madame Gazelle
What do we have here?
An old comic book
It's my favourite comic book!
A tin toy
It's my favourite toy!
A record
It's my favourite record!
And a very old carrot
That's mine
Good choice, Mummy
And a videotape of your daddies and mummies
when they were little
Who is that little pig wearing glasses?
Oh, that's Daddy
That's me
Hello, future!
Your voice was so squeaky when you were little!
You probably live on the Moon now
Daddy was so silly when he was little!
Making a time capsule is so much fun
But finding a time capsule is even more fun!